[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 19, "question": "Have you ever been in bad shape your whole life?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "been", "in", "bad", "shape", "your", "whole", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 20, "answer": "Yes, I've been in bad shape.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "in", "bad", "shape", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Seth, I've never met you, have I?", "question_tokens": ["Seth", ",", "I", "'ve", "never", "met", "you", ",", "have", "I", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "And do you understand why people like you and I never win the Emmy?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "understand", "why", "people", "like", "you", "and", "I", "never", "win", "the", "Emmy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "-- an Emmy to an atheist?", "question_tokens": ["--", "an", "Emmy", "to", "an", "atheist", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I mean, it's -- I don't know if it's that specific, but I think it's -- I think the Emmys do tend to make safe choices.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "it", "'s", "that", "specific", ",", "but", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "--", "I", "think", "the", "Emmys", "do", "tend", "to", "make", "safe", "choices", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "Do you think the fact that you're politically outspoken plays a role in maybe not winning awards?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "'re", "politically", "outspoken", "plays", "a", "role", "in", "maybe", "not", "winning", "awards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "It's possible.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "And you don't?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "do", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "I mean, this -- your \"Family Guy\" has been on what, 11 years?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "this", "--", "your", "``", "Family", "Guy", "''", "has", "been", "on", "what", ",", "11", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP$", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "WP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "You don't want to wrap it up, do you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "wrap", "it", "up", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "You'll do it as long as they'll let you, won't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ll", "do", "it", "as", "long", "as", "they", "'ll", "let", "you", ",", "wo", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "I think at this point, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "at", "this", "point", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 168, "question": "What are you disappointed in?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "disappointed", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "I feel like if I knew, if I was in those little rooms or those big rooms --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "like", "if", "I", "knew", ",", "if", "I", "was", "in", "those", "little", "rooms", "or", "those", "big", "rooms", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill"]}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Now why, of all the causes, not that we don't agree that that should have been done, but why that?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "why", ",", "of", "all", "the", "causes", ",", "not", "that", "we", "do", "n't", "agree", "that", "that", "should", "have", "been", "done", ",", "but", "why", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Well, Bill, good a time as any to make this announcement.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Bill", ",", "good", "a", "time", "as", "any", "to", "make", "this", "announcement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Beverly Hills"]}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Is there always locusts?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "always", "locusts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Not in Beverly Hills, but I mean --", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "in", "Beverly", "Hills", ",", "but", "I", "mean", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "``", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 213, "question": "How do you do it when they're all talking together in the same scene?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "do", "it", "when", "they", "'re", "all", "talking", "together", "in", "the", "same", "scene", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Well, when we do table reads for the shows, I -- it's a necessity, I have to jump around, you know, \"Hey, Quagmire, how's it going?\"", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "we", "do", "table", "reads", "for", "the", "shows", ",", "I", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "necessity", ",", "I", "have", "to", "jump", "around", ",", "you", "know", ",", "``", "Hey", ",", "Quagmire", ",", "how", "'s", "it", "going", "?", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "So that was your tribute to -- I remember when that played, that was this whole hour episode, right, because that was, for some reason, something that was very influential in your childhood, \"Star Wars,\" right?", "question_tokens": ["So", "that", "was", "your", "tribute", "to", "--", "I", "remember", "when", "that", "played", ",", "that", "was", "this", "whole", "hour", "episode", ",", "right", ",", "because", "that", "was", ",", "for", "some", "reason", ",", "something", "that", "was", "very", "influential", "in", "your", "childhood", ",", "``", "Star", "Wars", ",", "''", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "IN", "VBN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Yes, you know, I mean, my generation has -- grew up with that and it's, like it or not, we all know it backwards and forwards.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "my", "generation", "has", "--", "grew", "up", "with", "that", "and", "it", "'s", ",", "like", "it", "or", "not", ",", "we", "all", "know", "it", "backwards", "and", "forwards", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "I was actually more of a --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "actually", "more", "of", "a", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "You can't have both?", "question_tokens": ["You", "ca", "n't", "have", "both", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "How old were you when you made that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "were", "you", "when", "you", "made", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "I was about 2 years old, I think.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "about", "2", "years", "old", ",", "I", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "You did do that at 2?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "do", "that", "at", "2", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "CD", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "I was, what, 20?", "question_tokens": ["I", "was", ",", "what", ",", "20", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Oh, 20, OK.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "20", ",", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "``", "JJ", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "What do you think of shows like \"American Idol,\" the singing and \"The Voice\" and all these singing contests that are on TV?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "shows", "like", "``", "American", "Idol", ",", "''", "the", "singing", "and", "``", "The", "Voice", "''", "and", "all", "these", "singing", "contests", "that", "are", "on", "TV", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "``", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "''", "DT", "NN", "CC", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "CC", "DT", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "I've maybe seen \"American Idol\" twice.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "maybe", "seen", "``", "American", "Idol", "''", "twice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "``", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 341, "question": "You've avoided it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "avoided", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "I've never seen \"The Voice.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "never", "seen", "``", "The", "Voice", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Does that count?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "count", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "I've mentioned it before.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "mentioned", "it", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 349, "question": "What about procedural crime shows?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "procedural", "crime", "shows", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "It's tough to get --", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "tough", "to", "get", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "You are that bear?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "that", "bear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "You're in that bear costume?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "in", "that", "bear", "costume", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "I'm -- yes, I'm in the bear costume.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "--", "yes", ",", "I", "'m", "in", "the", "bear", "costume", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dupree"]}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "``", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "So if you were pitching it, and you had to do something meets something, what would it be?", "question_tokens": ["So", "if", "you", "were", "pitching", "it", ",", "and", "you", "had", "to", "do", "something", "meets", "something", ",", "what", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "I'd say, hey, it's \"You, Me and Dupree\" with fuzz.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "say", ",", "hey", ",", "it", "'s", "``", "You", ",", "Me", "and", "Dupree", "''", "with", "fuzz", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Who does she play?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "does", "she", "play", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "She plays --", "answer_tokens": ["She", "plays", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Wahlberg"]}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Of the bear?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "the", "bear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "The love interest of Mark Wahlberg.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "love", "interest", "of", "Mark", "Wahlberg", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "So you don't get the girl?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "do", "n't", "get", "the", "girl", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "No, no, I do not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "I", "do", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "It did?", "question_tokens": ["It", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "We're never going to see that?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'re", "never", "going", "to", "see", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Well, at some point in the future you may.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "at", "some", "point", "in", "the", "future", "you", "may", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Is it not?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Kind of the other problem.", "answer_tokens": ["Kind", "of", "the", "other", "problem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "That, you know, there were a number of issues with -- the predominant issue was schedule, but you know, there was -- it was a challenge to -- in a world where there are so many animated fathers on television who can trace their cartoon lineage directly back to Fred Flintstone, where does Fred Flintstone fit in himself?", "question_tokens": ["That", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "were", "a", "number", "of", "issues", "with", "--", "the", "predominant", "issue", "was", "schedule", ",", "but", "you", "know", ",", "there", "was", "--", "it", "was", "a", "challenge", "to", "--", "in", "a", "world", "where", "there", "are", "so", "many", "animated", "fathers", "on", "television", "who", "can", "trace", "their", "cartoon", "lineage", "directly", "back", "to", "Fred", "Flintstone", ",", "where", "does", "Fred", "Flintstone", "fit", "in", "himself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Fred Flintstone", "Fred Flintstone"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "You're bringing that back on FOX?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "bringing", "that", "back", "on", "FOX", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Right on regular TV?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "on", "regular", "TV", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "WP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "So what is that -- what can people look forward to with that show?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "is", "that", "--", "what", "can", "people", "look", "forward", "to", "with", "that", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "TO", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "Well, fans of the original will know more or less what to look for.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "fans", "of", "the", "original", "will", "know", "more", "or", "less", "what", "to", "look", "for", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "One of your heroes, right?", "question_tokens": ["One", "of", "your", "heroes", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Yes, absolutely, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "absolutely", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "One of the very influential writer -- and the last guy to really bridge the gap between science and between academia and -- is that word, academia?", "question_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "very", "influential", "writer", "--", "and", "the", "last", "guy", "to", "really", "bridge", "the", "gap", "between", "science", "and", "between", "academia", "and", "--", "is", "that", "word", ",", "academia", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ":", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "CC", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Academia.", "answer_tokens": ["Academia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "-- kind of really one or the other, right?", "question_tokens": ["--", "kind", "of", "really", "one", "or", "the", "other", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "CD", "CC", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "The problem is that if I tell you, hey, there's a monster living under my bed, you would say, well, that sounds ridiculous.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "problem", "is", "that", "if", "I", "tell", "you", ",", "hey", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "monster", "living", "under", "my", "bed", ",", "you", "would", "say", ",", "well", ",", "that", "sounds", "ridiculous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Are you an exercise nut?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "an", "exercise", "nut", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "RMSTRONG: I'm a -- yes.", "answer_tokens": ["RMSTRONG", ":", "I", "'m", "a", "--", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "And -- have you ever been in bad shape in your whole life?", "question_tokens": ["And", "--", "have", "you", "ever", "been", "in", "bad", "shape", "in", "your", "whole", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "CD", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "What is it asking for?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "asking", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Well, Prop 29 is a -- is a price increase on a pack of cigarettes in the state of California.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Prop", "29", "is", "a", "--", "is", "a", "price", "increase", "on", "a", "pack", "of", "cigarettes", "in", "the", "state", "of", "California", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Well, it's certainly safe to say that the gloves are off here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "certainly", "safe", "to", "say", "that", "the", "gloves", "are", "off", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "And I guess it's a little dated there, Lance, because at that point, you'd only won the Tour de France five times and you've actually won it seven, didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "guess", "it", "'s", "a", "little", "dated", "there", ",", "Lance", ",", "because", "at", "that", "point", ",", "you", "'d", "only", "won", "the", "Tour", "de", "France", "five", "times", "and", "you", "'ve", "actually", "won", "it", "seven", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "EX", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Yes, at the time, only five of them.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "at", "the", "time", ",", "only", "five", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lance"], "LOCATION": ["France"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Is it a mental thing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "mental", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "RMSTRONG: No, I mean I think there's certainly a mental part of this.", "answer_tokens": ["RMSTRONG", ":", "No", ",", "I", "mean", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "certainly", "a", "mental", "part", "of", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Is it not very just painful at a certain point?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "not", "very", "just", "painful", "at", "a", "certain", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "It depends how you describe pain.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "depends", "how", "you", "describe", "pain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Do you see him when you're in Texas?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "see", "him", "when", "you", "'re", "in", "Texas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "You know, I -- I -- I saw the former president about a year ago.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "--", "I", "--", "I", "saw", "the", "former", "president", "about", "a", "year", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}}]